Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1 MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: 1961 and Later, 1936-2015; 50 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Astronauts (1) (Offsite-box 468)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Astronauts (1) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Astronauts (2) (Offsite-box 468)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Astronauts (2) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 468, Folder 24)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Supplements and Life Society (Offsite-box 468-469)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Tax round table (Offsite-box 469, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-Feb. (Offsite-box 469, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Miscellaneous: March-April (Offsite-box 468, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Miscellaneous: May-June (Offsite-box 469, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1962: Edit: Miscellaneous: Oct.-Dec. (Offsite-box 469, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1962: Publishing (1) (Offsite-box 469, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1962: Publishing (2) (Offsite-box 469, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 469)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 469, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Supplements and Premium Editions and Life Society (Offsite-box 469, Folder 13-15)
  - Life: 1962-1963: Edit: Religion and Science Project (Offsite-box 469, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Russia Issue (Offsite-box 469, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Miscellaneous (1) (Offsite-box 469, Folder 18-19)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Miscellaneous (2) (Offsite-box 469, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1963: Edit: Role of Mass Magazine in U.S. by Austell and Grundwald (Offsite-box 469, Folder 21-22)
  - Life: 1963 (1964): Edit: Oppenheimer Teller (Offsite-box 469, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1963: Publishing (Offsite-box 470, Folder 1)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 470, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Miscellaneous (1) (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Miscellaneous (1) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1964: Edit: Miscellaneous (2) (Offsite-box 470, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1964: Publishing (Offsite-box 470, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 470, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Hycon Machine (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Hycon Machine [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1965: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1965: Publishing (Offsite-box 470, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 470, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Levi Smith Family Series (Offsite-box 470, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Photography Issue (Offsite-box 470, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1966: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1966: Publishing (Offsite-box 470, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Astronauts [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 470, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Investigative Reporting (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Investigative Reporting [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1967: Publishing (Offsite-box 470, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1967: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 470, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Miscellaneous (1) (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Miscellaneous (1) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Picasso Issue (Offsite-box 470, Folder 27)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Miscellaneous (2) (Offsite-box 470)
  - Life: 1968: Edit: Miscellaneous (2) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1968: Film Dept. (Offsite-box 471)
  - Life: 1968: Film Dept. [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 471, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 471, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Comment: Oil Slick (Offsite-box 471, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Investigative Reporting (Offsite-box 471, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Supplements (1) (Offsite-box 471, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Supplements (2) (Offsite-box 471, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-May (Offsite-box 471, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1969: Edit: Miscellaneous: June-Dec. (Offsite-box 471, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1969: Film Dept. (Offsite-box 471, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1969: Financial Analyses (Offsite-box 471, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1969: Publishing (Offsite-box 471, Folder 13-14)
  - Life: 1970: Financial Analyses (Offsite-box 471, Folder 15-16)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 471, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Personnel Evaluation (Offsite-box 471, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Comment: Veteran's Hospitals (Offsite-box 471, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Comment: Myra Breckenridge, etc (Offsite-box 471, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Guest Privilege (Offsite-box 471, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Investigative Reporting: Cervantes Article (Offsite-box 471, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Investigative Reporting (Offsite-box 471)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Investigative Reporting [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Khrushchev Remembers (Offsite-box 471, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Staff Dinner (Offsite-box 471, Folder 26)
  - Life: 1970 and Later: Edit: Supplements (Offsite-box 471, Folder 27)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Miscellaneous: Jan.-May (Offsite-box 471, Folder 28)
  - Life: 1970: Edit: Miscellaneous: June-Dec. (Offsite-box 472, Folder 1-2)
  - Life: 1970: Publishing (Offsite-box 472, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1971 and Later: Edit: Astronauts (Offsite-box 472, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 472, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Comment: Defense Dept. Story (Offsite-box 472, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Guest Privilege (Offsite-box 472, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Investigative Reporting (Offsite-box 472, Folder 8)
  - Life: 10/8/1971: Edit: Leadership Article (Offsite-box 472, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Third Century Series (Offsite-box 472, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1971 7 Later: Edit: Bicentennial Photo Contest (Offsite-box 472, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1971: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 472, Folder 12-13)
  - Life: 1971: Publishing (1) (Offsite-box 472, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1971: Publishing (2) (Offsite-box 472, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1971: Publishing (3) (Offsite-box 472, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1971: Publishing: Financial Analyses (Offsite-box 472, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1972: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 472, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1972: Edit: Investigative Reporting (Offsite-box 472, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1972: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 472, Folder 20-21)
  - Life: 1972: Edit: Financial Analyses (Offsite-box 472, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1972: Edit (Offsite-box 472, Folder 23-24)
  - Life: 1972: Publicity about Life's demise (Offsite-box 472, Folder 25-26)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: Jan.-May (Offsite-box 472-473)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: June-Sept. (Offsite-box 473)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: June-Sept. [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: Oct.-Dec. (Offsite-box 473, Folder 4-5)
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: Suspension Announc. Press Conference (Offsite-box 473, Folder 6-8)
    1 audiotape reel: analog. Label: "Life Staff Meeting (Tape 2 of 2) - 12/8/1972".
    1 audiotape reel: analog. Label: "Life Press Conf. (Tape 1 of 2) - 12/8/1972".
    1 audiotape reel: analog. Label: "Life Press Conf. (Tape 2 of 2) - 12/8/1972".
  - Life: 1972: Publishing: Suspension Announc. Staff Meeting (Offsite-box 473, Folder 9)
    1 audiotape reel: analog. Label: "Life Staff Meeting (Tape 1 of 2) - 12/8/1972".
  - Life: 1973 (Offsite-box 473)
  - Life: 1973 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life Special Report: 1973 (Offsite-box 473)
  - Life Special Report: 1973 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life Special Reports: 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 473, Folder 14-15)
  - Life: 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 473)
  - Life: 1974-1977 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1977: Edit: Banks Report (Offsite-box 473, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1978: Publishing: Weekly Reports (Offsite-box 473, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1978: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 474, Folder 1)
  - Life: 1978: Edit (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1978: Edit [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1978: Publishing: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 474, Folder 3-4)
  - Life: 1979: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 474, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1979: Edit (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1979: Edit [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1979: Publishing: Weekly Reports (Offsite-box 474, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1979: Publishing: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 474, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1980: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 474, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1980: Publishing (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1980: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1981: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1981: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1981: Publishing (Offsite-box 474, Folder 13)
  - Life: 1982: Publishing (Offsite-box 474, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1982: Edit (Offsite-box 474, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1983: Edit (Offsite-box 474, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1983: Publishing (Offsite-box 474, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1984: Edit (Offsite-box 474, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1984: Publishing (Offsite-box 474, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1985: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 474, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1985: Publishing (Offsite-box 474, Folder 21)
  - Life: 1986: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1986: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1986: Publishing (Offsite-box 474, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1987: Edit (Offsite-box 474, Folder 24)
  - Life: 1987: Publishing (Offsite-box 474, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1988: Edit (Offsite-box 474, Folder 26)
  - Life: 1988: Publishing (Offsite-box 474, Folder 27)
  - Life: 1989: Edit (Offsite-box 474, Folder 28)
  - Life: 1989: Publishing (Offsite-box 474, Folder 29)
  - Life: 1990: Edit (Offsite-box 475, Folder 1)
  - Life: 1990: Publishing (Offsite-box 475, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1991: Edit (Offsite-box 475, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1991: Edit: Special Weekly Issues: Persian Gulf War (Offsite-box 475, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1991: Publishing (Offsite-box 475, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1992: Edit (Offsite-box 475, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1992: Publishing (Offsite-box 475, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1993: Edit (Offsite-box 475, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1993: Publishing (Offsite-box 475, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1994: Edit (Offsite-box 475, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1994: Publishing (Offsite-box 475)
  - Life: 1994: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 2000: Last Issue (Offsite-box 475, Folder 12)
  - Life Group: 2004: Edit and Pub. (Offsite-box 475, Folder 13)
  - Life International: 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 14-15)
  - Life International: 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 16)
  - Life International: 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 17-18)
  - Life International: 1969 and Later (Offsite-box 475, Folder 19-20)
  - Life: Newspaper Supplement: Introduced 2004 [empty] (Offsite-box 475, Folder 21)
  - Life Spanish: 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 22-23)
  - Life Spanish: 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 24)
  - Life Special Reports: 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 475)
  - Life Special Reports: 1976-1977 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Little Brown & Co. (Offsite-box 475, Folder 26-27)
  - Magazine Administrative Services: 1987- (Offsite-box 475, Folder 28)
  - Mad Magazine: 1992- (Offsite-box 476, Folder 1)
  - Magazine Administrative Services: The Time Inc. Magazine Store (Offsite-box 476, Folder 2)
  - Magazine Administrative Services: 1988 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 3)
  - Magazine Communications (Offsite-box 476, Folder 4)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1963-6/1973 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 5)
  - Magazine Development: General: 7/1973-12/1973 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 6)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1974 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 7)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 8-9)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 10-11)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1985- (Offsite-box 476, Folder 12)
  - Magazine Group: 1980-1981: American Renewal (Offsite-box 476)
  - Magazine Group: 1980-1981: American Renewal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Magazine Group: 1981-: Financial & Development Group (Offsite-box 476, Folder 14)
  - Magazine Group: 1969-1986: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 476, Folder 15)
  - Magazine Group: 1987-1989: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 476)
  - Magazine Group: 1987-1989: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Magazine Group: 1990- (Offsite-box 476, Folder 18)
  - Magazine Manufacturing and Distribution: 1987-Oct. 1992 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 19)
  - Magazine Manufacturing Services (Offsite-box 476, Folder 20)
  - Manhattan Cable T.V.: 1965-1972 (Offsite-box 476)
  - Manhattan Cable T.V.: 1965-1972 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Manhattan Cable: 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 477)
  - Manhattan Cable: 1973-1975 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Manhattan Cable: 1976-1987 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 3)
  - Manhattan Cable: 1988- (Offsite-box 477, Folder 4)
  - March of Time: Movie (Offsite-box 477)
  - March of Time: Movie [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - March of Time: Movie: 1975 & Later: Possible Broadway Show Adaption (Offsite-box 477)
  - March of Time: Movie: 1975 & Later: Possible Broadway Show Adaption [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - March of Time: Radio (Offsite-box 477, Folder 8)
  - Martha Stewart Living Enterprises (Offsite-box 477, Folder 9)
  - Money: 1970 and Before: Origins (Offsite-box 477, Folder 10)
  - Money: 1971: Circulation Promotion (Offsite-box 477, Folder 11)
  - Money: 1971: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 477, Folder 12)
  - Money: 1971: Prospectus (Offsite-box 477, Folder 13)
  - Money: 1972: Edit: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 477, Folder 14)
  - Money: 1972: Edit: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 477, Folder 15)
  - Money: 1972: First Issue (Offsite-box 477, Folder 16)
  - Money: 1973: Promotion: Adv. and Circ. (Offsite-box 477, Folder 17)
  - Money: 1972: Publicity (Offsite-box 477, Folder 18)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: Jan.-March (Offsite-box 477)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: Jan.-March [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: April-June (Offsite-box 477, Folder 20)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: July-Sept. (Offsite-box 477, Folder 21)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: Oct.-Dec. (Offsite-box 477, Folder 22)
  - Money: 1973: Edit (Offsite-box 477, Folder 23)
  - Money: 1973: Publishing (Offsite-box 477, Folder 24)
  - Money: 1974: Edit (Offsite-box 477, Folder 25)
  - Money: 1974: Publishing (Offsite-box 477, Folder 26)
  - Money: 1975: Board of Directors: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 477, Folder 27)
  - Money: 1975: Edit (Offsite-box 477, Folder 28)
  - Money: 1972: Dummies (Offsite-box 477, Folder 29)
  - Money: 1975: Publishing (Offsite-box 477, Folder 30-31)
  - Money: 1976: Edit [empty] (Offsite-box 477, Folder 32)
  - Money: 1976: Publishing (Offsite-box 477, Folder 33)
  - Money: 1977: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 1)
  - Money: 1977: Publishing [empty] (Offsite-box 478, Folder 2)
  - Money: 1978: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 3)
  - Money: 1978: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 4)
  - Money: 1979: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 5)
  - Money: 1979: Publishing [empty] (Offsite-box 478, Folder 6)
  - Money: 1980: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 7)
  - Money: 1980: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 8)
  - Money: 1981: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 9)
  - Money: 1981: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 10)
  - Money: 1982: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 11)
  - Money: 1982: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 12)
  - Money: 1983: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 13)
  - Money: 1983: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 14)
  - Money: 1984: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 15)
  - Money: 1984: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 16)
  - Money: 1985: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 478, Folder 17)
  - Money: 1985: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 18)
  - Money: 1986: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 478, Folder 19)
  - Money: 1986: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 20)
  - Money: 1987: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 21)
  - Money: 1987: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 22)
  - Money: 1988: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 23)
  - Money: 1988: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 24)
  - Money: 1989: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 25)
  - Money: 1989: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 26)
  - Money: 1990: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 27)
  - Money: 1990: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 28)
  - Money: 1991: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 29)
  - Money: 1991: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 30)
  - Money: 1992: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 31)
  - Money: 1992: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 32)
  - Money: 1993: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 33)
  - Money: 1993: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 34)
  - Money: 1994: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 35)
  - Money: 1994: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 36)
  - Money: 1995: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 37)
  - Money: 1995: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 38)
  - Money: 1996: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 39)
  - Money: 1996: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 40)
  - Money: 1997: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 41)
  - Money: 1997: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 42)
  - Money Japan: 1985- (Offsite-box 478, Folder 43)
  - Money: 1997: Your Company [empty] (Offsite-box 478, Folder 44)
  - Mutual Funds: 1998: Edit and Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 45)
  - Newsbureau [empty] (Offsite-box 478, Folder 46)
  - Money: 1989: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 9)
  - Money: 1990: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 10)
  - Money: 1990: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 11)
  - Money: 1991: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 12)
  - Money: 1991: Publishing (Offsite-box 478, Folder 13)
  - Money: 1992: Edit (Offsite-box 478, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: 1948-1965: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 478, Folder 47)
  - Newspapers: 1966-1967: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 478, Folder 48-49)
  - Newspapers: 1968-1969: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 478, Folder 50)
  - Newspapers: 1970-: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 478, Folder 51)
  - New York Graphic Society Ltd.: 1966-1981 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 52)
  - Nuts (Offsite-box 478, Folder 53)
  - Offices: Chicago (Offsite-box 478, Folder 54)
  - Offices: New York (Offsite-box 478, Folder 55)
  - Panorama: 1962-1969: Argentina (Offsite-box 478)
  - Panorama: 1962-1969: Argentina [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - Panorama: Italy: Dummies and First Issue (Offsite-box 478, Folder 58-59)
  - Panorama: 1960-1961: Italy (Offsite-box 478, Folder 60)
  - Panorama: 1962: Italy (Offsite-box 479, Folder 1)
  - Panorama: 1963: Italy (Offsite-box 479, Folder 2)
  - Panorama: 1964-1965: Italy (Offsite-box 479, Folder 3)
  - Parenting: 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 4)
  - Parenting: 1988- (Offsite-box 479, Folder 5)
  - People: 1973: Dummies (1) (Offsite-box 479, Folder 6)
  - People: 1973: Dummies (2) (Offsite-box 479, Folder 7)
  - People: 1973: Dummies (3) (Offsite-box 479, Folder 8-9)
  - People: 1973: Dummies (4) (Offsite-box 479, Folder 10)
  - People: 1973 and Before: Origins (Offsite-box 479, Folder 11)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Edit (Offsite-box 479, Folder 12)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 479, Folder 13)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Publishing: May-July (Offsite-box 479, Folder 14)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Publishing: Aug.-Oct. (Offsite-box 479, Folder 15-16)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Publishing: Nov.-Dec. (Offsite-box 479, Folder 17)
  - People: 1973: Prospectus (Offsite-box 479, Folder 18)
  - People: 1973: Publicity (Offsite-box 479, Folder 19)
  - People: 3/4/1974: First Issue (Offsite-box 479, Folder 20)
  - People: 1974: Edit: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 479, Folder 21)
  - People: 1974: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 479, Folder 22)
  - People: 1974: Publicity (Offsite-box 479, Folder 23)
  - People: 1974: Publishing: Jan.-March (Offsite-box 480)
  - People: 1974: Publishing: Jan.-March [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - People: 1974: Publishing: April-June (Offsite-box 480, Folder 2)
  - People: 1974: Publishing: July-Sept. (Offsite-box 480, Folder 3)
  - People: 1975: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 5)
  - People: 1975: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 6)
  - People: 1976: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 7)
  - People: 1976: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 8)
  - People: 1977: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 9)
  - People: 1977: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 10)
  - People: 1978: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 11)
  - People: 1978: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 12)
  - People: 1979: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 13)
  - People: 1979: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 14)
  - People: 1980: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 480, Folder 15)
  - People: 1980: Publishing (Offsite-box 480)
  - People: 1980: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - People: 1981: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 480, Folder 17)
  - People: 1981: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 18)
  - People: 1982: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 19)
  - People: 1982: Publishing (Offsite-box 480)
  - People: 1982: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R5)
  - People: 1983: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 21)
  - People: 1983: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 22-23)
  - People: 1984: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 480, Folder 24)
  - People: 1984: 10th Anniversary Issue (Offsite-box 480, Folder 25)
  - People: 1984: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 26)
  - People: 1986: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 27)
  - People: 1986: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 28)
  - People: 1986: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 29)
  - People: 1987: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 30)
  - People: 1987: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 31)
  - People: 1988: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 32)
  - People: 1988: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 33)
  - People: 1989: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 34)
  - People: 1989: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 35)
  - People: 1990: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 36)
  - People: 1990: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 37)
  - People: 1991: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 38)
  - People: 1991: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 39)
  - People: 1992: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 40)
  - People: 1992: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 41)
  - People: 1993: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 42)
  - People: 1994: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 44)
  - People: 1994: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 45)
  - People: 1994: 20th Anniversary (Offsite-box 480, Folder 46)
  - People: 1995: Edit [empty] (Offsite-box 480, Folder 47)
  - People: 1995-1996: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 48)
  - People: 1997-1999: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 49)
  - People: 1997-1998: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 50)
  - People: 2000: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 51)
  - People: 2004: Edit: 30th Anniversary (Offsite-box 480, Folder 52)
  - People: 2001-: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 53)
  - People en Espanol: 1997-: Edit (Offsite-box 480, Folder 54)
  - People en Espanol: 1997-: Publishing (Offsite-box 480, Folder 55)
  - People Group: 1998- (Offsite-box 480, Folder 56)
  - People International: 1991-: Who Weekly (Offsite-box 480, Folder 57)
  - People Style Watch: February 2007: First Issue (Offsite-box 480, Folder 58)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities: 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 58)